healthnews.com 2013-05-21

# HealthNews Privacy Policy

At HealthNews, we take your privacy seriously. We will never use your personal information in a way that would identify you to an outside party and we will never sell or distribute the information you provide us without your express consent. 

The Bottom Line: We don't like it when people misuse our personal information and we're going to make sure we don't misuse yours.

For the complete details about how we handle your private information, please read our privacy policy below. If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us.

##  HealthNews Privacy Policy 

Welcome to the website HealthNews.com, operated by Health News, Inc. (“HealthNews” or “us” or “we”). The term “you” or “your” refers to the user or viewer of HealthNews.com, including any related websites maintained by HealthNews, such as the HealthNewsUS Twitter page (collectively, the “Sites”).

YOUR USE OF THE SITES OR PROVISION OF ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION TO HEALTHNEWS OR THROUGH THE SITES CONSTITUTES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THIS POLICY. DO NOT USE THE SITES OR PROVIDE INFORMATION (OR ALLOW OTHERS TO DO SO ON YOUR BEHALF) IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

This Privacy Policy is part of and incorporated into the Terms and Conditions of Use for the Sites (“TOU”), which is the contract between you and HealthNews governing use of the Sites. Parts of the TOU affect this Privacy Policy; so, unless you have already done so, please review the [Terms of Use](http://www.healthnews.com/Terms) prior to using the Sites. Capitalized terms used but not defined in this Privacy Policy have the definitions provided in the TOU. 

This Privacy Policy describes the information collected from you when visiting the Sites and how it may be used, including any further disclosure of such information to third parties.

##  Personally Identifiable Information

The term "Personally Identifiable Information" means your full name, physical address, email address, telephone number, or any other personal information that, alone or in combination with other information, permits us or third parties to identify or contact you physically or online.

We collect Personally Identifiable Information that you provide to the Sites when you: (1) become a registered user; (2) create your personal profile; or (3) submit requests, suggestions, or other communications to us. The information we typically will collect include: (1) user name and (2) email address. It is always your choice, or the choice of anyone acting for you, whether to provide Personally Identifiable Information. Do not provide Personally Identifiable Information about others without their permission. By submitting any Personally Identifiable Information about others, you represent and warrant that you are authorized to do so.

The Personally Identifiable Information is primarily used for internal review, to improve content of the Sites, to notify visitors about updates to the Sites, and may be used by us to contact visitors for marketing purposes. Additionally, in the course of providing you with the services you find on the Sites, our web and application servers will automatically collect usage-related information, including the URLs that you access through the Sites, the date and time of your usage, your Internet protocol (IP) address, your Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exist pages, platform type, date/time stamp, number of clicks and your browser type. We collect this information so we can perform effective capacity planning, administer the Sites, troubleshoot the Sites’ performance, track users’ movements in the aggregate, gather demographic information for aggregate use and accurately document revenue-generating transactions for our business partners.

##  Third Parties with Whom We May Share Information

We may disclose any non-public Personally Identifiable Information and usage-related information about you to nonaffiliated third parties without your consent for the conduct of our business, for commercial purposes, or as required or permitted by law, such as, (1) to respond to a subpoena or court order, judicial process, law enforcement or regulatory authorities; (2) in connection with a proposed or actual sale, merger, or transfer of all or a portion of business or an operating unit; (3) to consumer reporting agencies; or (4) prevent fraud or other illegal activities from being perpetrated. Any commercial use of the above-mentioned information will comply with the requirements of the CAN-SPAM Act.

We may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to insurance companies for the purposes of making a claim.

We may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to affiliated companies or business successors to HealthNews.

We may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to any third party whom you have consented to receive your personal information.

## Links 

The Sites may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices, the terms and conditions of use, or any of the content of such sites. The linked sites may collect Personally Identifiable Information from you that is not subject to our control. The data collection practices of linked sites will be governed by that site’s privacy policy

##  Security Measures

We are committed to maintaining the security of information under our control. To safeguard and secure the information we collect, we have put in place appropriate security procedures and controls. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect, and we cannot control the actions of third parties with whom you choose to share information. We are not responsible for circumvention of any security measures by third parties.

##  Public Areas

Any information that you choose to disclose in public areas on the Sites, such as your comment postings will be publicly available and accessible to third parties. Any such disclosures are made at your own risk.

##  Cookies 

We may use Cookies to monitor the Sites’ usage, advertisement viewing, and performance and to personalize the content of various areas within the Sites. The information collected by Cookies (i) helps us dynamically generate advertising and content on the Sites or in newsletters, (ii) allows us to statistically monitor how many people are using the Sites and selected sponsors' and advertisers' sites, (iii) how many people open our emails, and (iv) for what purposes these actions are being taken. We may use Cookie information to deliver certain advertisements to your browser on our owned or operated websites based on areas of the Sites that you have visited during the same session or to determine the popularity of certain content or advertisements. Cookies are also used to facilitate a user's log-in, as navigation aids and as session timers.

##  Children’s Privacy

We do not want to collect information from children. Do not provide any Personally Identifiable Information unless you are at least 13 years of age, and please caution your children not to provide any. If a child under 13 has provided Personally Identifiable Information, a parent or guardian may so inform us by writing us at our address below and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete it from our database, subject to applicable law and this Privacy Policy.

##  Distribution of Email Addresses

HealthNews generally does not sell, rent, or in any way share email addresses with other organizations, but may do so as may be required to help us operate and improve our website or programs. Email addresses may be used to identify you when you refer a friend to the Sites. We also reserve the right to transfer the email addresses we collect to any successor in interest.

##  Opt-Out Options for Email Newsletters

If you would like to opt-out of Health News newsletters, click on the Unsubscribe link located at both the top and bottom of the e-mail newsletter. If the e-mail does not contain an Unsubscribe link, it is the result of a transaction on HealthNews.com and will only be sent once.

## European Union Data Considerations

Personally Identifiable Information collected on the Sites may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which HealthNews or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Sites, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

##  Notice Of Changes To Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to make changes to our Privacy Policy. Any material changes and the effective date of those changes will be posted on the Sites. One of your responsibilities is to review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure that you are apprised of any changes. The Privacy Policy in effect at the time you provide your Personally Identifiable Information to us is what will govern our handling of your Personally Identifiable Information. Your continued use of the Sites after we post any material changes to this Privacy Policy signifies your acceptance of its terms, as modified.

##  Your Rights

You have the right to access the Personally Identifiable Information that HealthNews holds about you within the scope of applicable law. Please make any access request to HealthNews at the contact details given below. HealthNews will process your access request in accordance with its obligations under the relevant legislation and may charge you an administration fee to do so.

##  Contact Information

If you have any questions about our collection of personal information, this Privacy Policy or related matters, you may contact us at:

Health News, Inc. 5565 S. Decatur Blvd., Suite 101 Las Vegas, NV 89118 (702) 509-7999
